BRANDON CAPRIOTTI

Greater Washington, DC | 516.404.9693 | bcapriotti97@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/-bcapriotti

IT DEVELOPMENT | ACCOUNTING | AUDITING

Initiative-taking Accounting professional with early career experience with top accounting firm. Eye for details proven with both CPA firm clients and as university intern. Identifies opportunities to learn and then contribute new-found knowledge to successfully complete projects. Draws on education focused on accounting and computer information systems.

Areas of Expertise:

- Financial Accounting
- Corporate Auditing
- GAAP & IFRS
- Flowcharting & Visual Processes
- CIS Infrastructure
- HTML & CSS Coding
- Python Programming
- Cloud Management
- Data Analysis
- Systems Implementation
- IT Applications
- Remote/Virtual Office

Early Contributions

- Although new to aero-space/defense technology manufacturing, facilitated cycle count successfully and promptly executing all required procedures and documentation and upon completion, inspiring client commendation.
- Requested (and was granted) pension and trust fund investment test work project; independently researched pensions and trust fund investments. While pursuing (and completing) appropriate procedures, discovered client mistake and then avoided potentially difficult/costly ramifications.
- As an intern at James Madison University (JMU) International Accounting Dept, built Excel workbook that could determine exchange rates in over 100 participating countries taking all factors into consideration. Over three years later, workbook still used daily.

Professional Career Overview

KPMG | McLean, VA | 2019 - 2022

Audit Associate (2020-2022)

- Facilitated design and implementation tests as well as operating effectiveness on client internal controls.
- Performed and documented analytical procedures and detail tests related to financial statement audits.
- Conducted walk-throughs, cycle count observations and other client-facing auditing procedures.

Audit Intern (2019)

Assisted engagement team by documenting financial statement audit procedures; evaluated 3rd-party confirmations with client data to verify account balances and transaction history; reviewed and assessed financial statement data.

<u>Financial Reporting & International Accounting Intern | JMU | Harrisonburg, VA | 2018 – 2019</u>
Prepared and reconciled daily and monthly reports including Internal Control, Capital and Construction and Cash and Investments.

• Analyzed budgets and reconciliations for the 104 international study abroad program.

Testimonial

"His attention to detail and ability to learn quickly allowed us to provide coverage over a vacant position, while at the same time implementing new accounting regulations and managing regular year-end tasks."

- Ashley L. Comer, JMU Financial Reporting Director

Education

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration | James Madison University | 2015 - 2020